gamepacks.com 2015-03-14

# GamePacks– Free Games, Download And Play.

## Perion Privacy Policy

THIS STATEMENT APPLIES TO PERION NETWORK LTD. AND ITS SUBSIDIARIES’ (“PERION”) INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE POLICIES WITH RESPECT TO USE OF THE WEBSITE, SERVICES AND PRODUCTS.IT DOES NOT APPLY TO PERION'S SITES, SERVICES AND PRODUCTS THAT DO NOT DISPLAY OR LINK TO THIS STATEMENT OR THAT HAVE THEIR OWN PRIVACY STATEMENTS. BY USING THE WEBSITE, SERVICES OR PRODUCTS, YOU CONSENT TO THE DATA PRACTICES AND INFORMATION COLLECTION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS STATEMENT. PERION IS COMMITTED TO PRESERVING THE PRIVACY OF OUR USERS. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS WHICH INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN, DO NOT USE THE SERVICES, WEBSITES, AND PRODUCTS MADE AVAILABLE BY PERION (collectively, the “PERION SERVICES” or the “SERVICES”).

## THE SITE AND SERVICES 

We do not request nor collect any personal information from Users who simply visit Perion’s websites (“Website(s)”). Prior to and after downloading and use of any of Perion Services and Websites, Users will be asked to provide certain required and optional information, and information collected from your interaction with Perion Services(collectively “Information”), as described and explained more fully throughout this Privacy Policy. Some of the Perion Services will, among other things, enable Users to send Messages and/or Content to other people (both Users and non-Users). Subject to all general security limitations inherent in communicating via the Internet, a Message will not be generally accessible to Users or others who are not intended recipients of the Message. Please use the same discretion when sending Messages through the Service as you would when sending ordinary electronic mail. Perion may post from time to time newsletters, as well as subscribe/unsubscribe forms. These forms may ask for a valid email address. This information will be used solely for the purpose of subscription to or unsubscription from the Perion newsletter list. You will be provided with an opt-in choice to receive e-mail newsletters and updates upon registration.

As part of the Services, you may from time to time upload images, photos, documents, information and/or any other content (“Content”). You understand that the Content may include personally identifiable information which will be protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy and shall be considered as Information for the purpose of this privacy policy and will be used by Perion only for the purposes for which it was collected in order to provide the Services.

While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of the Information.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH USE OF THE SERVICES 

Perion may collect Information when you interact with the Perion Services, depending on how you use the Perion Services, the Information, may include: ****

a) Certain technical information gathered or received when you visit the Website or access/use the Perion Services including without limitation: the type of browser, operating system, ISP, location and Internet protocol (IP) address;

b) Information made available by you in public areas within the Website and/or the Services;

c) Registration-related information (such as name, home or work addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone and fax numbers, birth date or gender);

d) Transaction-related information (such as credit card or other preferred means of payment, (that we maintain in encrypted form on industry secure servers), billing or shipping information, or a history of products purchased through the Perion Services;

e) Information about your visits and use of the various Perion Services, offerings and advertisements that you view/use, how you use them, how frequently you use them, your responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on these Perion Services, and other related information regarding your usage of Perion Services;

f) Information about mobile devices used to access Perion including UDID (Unique Device Identifier);

g) In addition, many software versions provided by Perion (“Software”) are configured to automatically report back information relating to computer errors arising in connection with use of the Software, without notice to you. Information on your Software configuration settings may be included. This data is sent to Perion to help us diagnose performance issues with, and improve, the Software.

Your Information is usually automatically collected and stored in log files of the Services’ computer servers and may be supplemented with additional information from other companies.

## OUR USE OF THE INFORMATION 

Perion gathers Information in order to better understand how users, as a group, use the software and the various features thereof, as well as to help Perion tailor offerings to user groups with specific profiles, and to conduct market research. The parameters and the usage patterns may be used in the aggregate for commercial purposes, including without limitation, for marketing, co-registration to other services, promotional activities or any other activity, including, without limitation, the protection of Perion’s proprietary and other rights all subject to the provisions herein. Perion will process the Information only for specific and limited purposes. We ask for and collect data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes. Perion will use the Information to provide Users with important information about the Services (such as upgrades, modifications, etc.), to announce new products and services available to Users and to send you marketing and advertising material subject to your consent. You can decline to submit personally identifiable information, in which case Perion may not be able to provide you with Services ****

Perion will only use personally identifiable information to create aggregate, non-personal reports about the Users of the Service, and to generate aggregate statistical studies and conduct research related to the Services and the use of the Website and provide Users with certain content that may be of interest to that User based on the Information. We use and store this data only on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us to determine how and the extent to which certain parts of our Website and the Services are used.

Except as expressly set forth herein and/or as necessary to perform the functions of the Service, Perion will not share, sell or lease any personally identifiable information about any User to any third party for any secondary purposes without that User’s permission.

Perion only shares your personally identifiable information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing on our behalf.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request,  
(b) enforce applicable agreements and/or their terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof,  
(c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Perion, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets.

We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions, in compliance with this Privacy Policy and/or comply with adequate level of protection regarding the data and shall not further transfer the data.

## CHOICE; OPT OUT

Our Website provides Users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us. If you do not want to receive communications from us, please contact our customer service center in the following URL: <http://www.incredimail.com/english/help/support.aspx>

## ACCESS TO INFORMATION; UPDATE

A User may review and update his personal information provided by him by accessing the Software settings. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information is kept accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our Users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. Upon receipt of your written request and enough information to permit us to identify you, we will disclose to you the information we hold about you. We will also correct, amend or delete any personal information that is inaccurate and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. You agree that Perion may retain (but shall have no obligation to retain) your data for a limited reasonable period after your use of or license to Perion Services has been terminated, expired, or otherwise lapsed, for the sole purpose of enabling you to renew your use of or license to the Services shortly thereafter, after such period the data shall be erased.

## COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

“Cookies” are pieces of information that are placed on an individual’s computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Service and the Website. Perion may use cookies and other technologies to save certain information about a User and others who visit and interact with the Website and the Services, in order to facilitate and enhance Users interactions and activities with the Services and/or Website and to provide User with personalized content which may include interest based information, online ads or other marketing materials. Perion may use third party tracking services to analyze this information, help manage and optimize the Services and measure the effectiveness of its advertising and how visitors use the Website. To do this, Perion may use Web beacons and cookies or other technologies provided by these third parties on the Website or the Services. Such technologies may be able to collect the User IP address, User browsing data in connection with the Website, the Services or other sites or services outside of Perion. Perion may use and/or provide this information in the aggregate, and on anonymous basis, to its partners including for the purpose of delivering advertising that may be more relevant to you, and to help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. This information helps Perion learn things such as what pages are most attractive to visitors of the Website, which of Perion’s products most interest its customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see.

We may use an outside advertising company to display advertisements on the Website and Services. These third parties also may use cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies to, among other things, enable such third parties to record which ads your browser has loaded and which site pages you may have been viewing when the ads were delivered or accessed. Use of such third-party sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of those third parties. The advertisement company may also collect cookies received with outside ad banners. In addition, we may use third party advertisers to serve or track advertisements on websites. We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the advertising company. Perion does not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. By using any Perion Services, you have affirmatively consented to the collection of Information and cookies as described above.

## OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS

The Services may contain links to other Web sites. Perion is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Some of these offerings are provided by third parties who may provide you with additional information and choices about your privacy. If you choose to take advantage of these offerings, you should read the privacy policies of such third parties.

## SOCIAL NETWORK SERVICES 

Perion may offer to Users of Perion Services, additional features and services that provide access to social networks. The use of such social network is governed by the terms of such social network. You can sign in to your social network Website through some of Perion Services, features and services. When you elect to sign in, you will be asked to grant us access to certain information from your social network profile. This information may include friends or contacts lists, notes, updates and photos, and may be used by Perion to help you personalize your experience with Perion Services, suggest new features and content that may be relevant to you or provide Perion with data for statistical purposes. If you elect to permit Perion access this information, Perion will be able to see and use this information and thus you may be changing your preexisting privacy settings, however, Perion does not have control over privacy settings in your social network account. Please see your social network provider policies for any questions or concerns. All information gathered via social network services shall be considered as Information as referenced throughout this Privacy Policy. The Information will be protected and used by Perion in accordance with this Privacy Policy. It is important to stress that Perion does not sell or rent any personally identifiable information it compiles to any third parties. Perion may provide non-identifiable, general statistical and demographic information to its publishers from time to time. You may opt not to grant Perion access to your social network account(s) at any time by changing your social network settings or by not authorizing access. ****

## CHILDREN

If you are a child under the age of 18, you must obtain parental consent prior to using our Services. Perion will not knowingly contact or engage with children under the age of 18 without said parental consent. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided us with their personal information, please contact us at the address given above and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

## CONSENT TO PROCESSING/INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

By providing any personally identifiable information to us pursuant to this Privacy Policy, all users, including, without limitation, users in the United States, Israel and member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection and processing of such information abroad. The server on which the Website is hosted may be outside the country from which you access the Website and may be outside your country of residence. Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Privacy Policy may involve the transfer of your personally identifiable information to various countries around the world that may have different levels of privacy protection than your country. By submitting your personally identifiable information through the Services, you consent, acknowledge, and agree that we may collect, use, transfer, and disclose your personally identifiable information as described in this privacy policy. If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services.

## CHANGES TO THIS POLICY 

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on the Website or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of the Website and/or Services will constitute your acceptance of any modified Privacy Policy.

## ENFORCEMENT

Perion regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is Perion’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer the Information that cannot be resolved between Perion and an individual. ****

## CONTACT US 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email to: [privacy@perion.com](mailto:privacy@perion.com).

Last Updated: March 2015
